<?xml version="1.0"?>
<webpage id="designGoals">
  <config param="rcsdate" value="$Date: 2006/04/17 16:26:49 $"/>
  <head>
    <title>Design Goals</title>
    <summary>SilkPage Design Goals</summary>
    <keywords>Valid XHTML Code, Easy maintenance, Accessibility</keywords>
  </head>

  <para>
    When it comes to the website design and development, there's far too much 
    software tools that can be used; but none of them satisfied our design
    goals: 
    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          Web Standards compliant web pages based on XML
        </para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          Accessibility and usability
        </para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          Easy maintenance
        </para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
    We crafted SilkPage, having the above design goals in mind. SilkPage output
    web pages meet the above requirements.
  </para>

  <section id="cleancode">
    <title>Valid Code</title>
    <para>
      SilkPage output markup is validated <acronym>XHTML</acronym>. 
      No legacy XHTML such as nested
      layout tables and font tags, the page size is reduced dramatically and 
      the source code is easier to read and faster to load.
      At the back-end, SilkPage uses  DocBook Website Types together with 
      <acronym>XSL</acronym> stylesheets to produce customized 
      XHTML content. <emphasis>Web Standards compliant web pages</emphasis>.
    </para>
  </section>

  <section id="stylesheet">
    <title>Stylesheets Use</title>
    <para>
      Cascading Style Sheets (<acronym>CSS</acronym>) is used to separate 
      presentation from content. SilkPage makes use of CSS
      stylesheets by applying its CSS themes. 
      Look and feel of the site can be changed by simply applying a new 
      CSS theme. <emphasis>Ease of maintenance</emphasis>.
    </para>
  </section>

  <section id="accessibility">
    <title>Accessibility</title>
    <para>
      To serve people with visual or mobile impairments, SilkPage follows 
      accessibility guidelines closely:
      <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          Style sheets rather than deprecated markup like are used to present 
          content.
        </para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          SilkPage generates markup that is structural and meaningful. 
        </para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          Generated markup is not presented by graphics, graphics are not 
          necessary to understand the main content.
        </para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          The main navigation menu is short and tab based, all main content is 
          provided near the top of the document.
        </para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          Text equivalents are provided for every non-text element 
          (e.g., using "alt")
        </para>
      </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </para>
  </section>
</webpage>
